{
    "id": "836b3c210d0f4f1abd53e67befc153ae",
    "title": "Formation of Negatives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Martha ................... not live with her sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2a3b7ab0b2d34fa6af1292843b18c388"
        },
        {
            "question": "James ......................... not own three cars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42e1910460c54dc99df09ca573a6d3fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cats ................... not chase mice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e0df5cdd835424793df4f18f20eb5e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Birds ................... not make their nests in trees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9f04c58ae9b241d992b441aa35672fe3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Deciduous trees ...................... not shed their leaves in autumn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9f071439201c4550b577a26d71ec8b88"
        },
        {
            "question": "The earth ........................ not move around the sun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aef202878aee4b849f3b784f34858ae1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Honey ........................... not taste sweet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a1e28a451bd4d119f2d0d9df8daac70"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandparents ..................... not keep pigs in their shed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec09e2a612fb4317839c84e95ce37bd8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................... not work hard to support his family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ae7fbb314003476aad9fcf5c46519dd8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Opposite poles ..................... not attract.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "40824a6343204abcb3b1273ca4a187ba"
        }
    ]
}